Sensei, good work today.
Oh, I just got here, don't mind me.
Rather, I hope I won't get in the way of your work.
I'm the only one on duty today?
No, it's not that I mind or anything.
Anyway, where should I start helping today?
As usual, there's a huge pile of paperwork.
Well, the Prefect Team has a lot too, but we also have Ako and Chinatsu to help out.
Come to think of it, Sensei not only has us,
but fairies from all kinds of clubs and schools come here.
Alright, I'll start looking over here.
This one and this are done, it seems.
It's okay, I can figure most of it out.
If there's anything I'm unsure about, I'll ask you then.
After all, it would defeat the purpose if I troubled Sensei.
For paperwork to submit to the Student Council Federation, the Prefect Team uses similar formats, so I know what to do.
I'll borrow some stationery around here.
Let's see, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
This one and this, I'll go through everything first.
This goes here, and here, like so.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
And this one goes...
I think it was like this.
Hmm, wait a minute.
Hm?
I-It's okay, it's not heavy at all. I'm not in danger.
Not in danger. Yeah, leave it to me.
It's probably the format.
Name, address.
Hmm...
What else...
Sensei, I'll borrow this area.
It's the same as the invalid forms, right?
Yeah, I'll clean them up together.
This and...
Yeah.
Hmm...
Uh, let's see...
There's a misalignment here.
Oh.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's see...
Just to be sure, one more time.
Yeah.
Good work, Sensei. Did we make some progress?
Yes.
Sensei, you look tired.
I'll make some coffee for you.
May I use the kitchen?
It's okay. I know where it is, you sit tight.
Let's see...
I think it was...
Hmm...
Uh, let's see...
The varieties keep increasing.
Wait a minute.
Just a minute.
A little more.
Yeah.
Yes, alright.
Sorry for the wait, Sensei.
I made some coffee, but...
Have a sip.
Y-You don't have to be so eager about it.
It's hot out, so take your time.
Is it... good?
I see, I'm glad.
I don't usually make it myself,
so I was a little worried.
Ako normally makes it for me.
You didn't have to gulp it down like that.
I-I can't take your cup either.
You have to drink it.
There's no point otherwise.
Honestly.
The paperwork?
Ah, everything that was on that desk over there is done.
But there are some parts that need you to look over, Sensei.
I have time now.
Okay, first...
The stamp is missing here.
And the back side is also required here, so be careful.
This part and this part.
Right.
Here and here.
Also this border section.
I think you should look over this stack, Sensei.
There's some tricky stuff written inside.
Yeah, that's right.
It's together with that paperwork, so if you look it over, you'll understand.
The records for that time are in this folder.
With these two, you should be able to make a judgment.
The rest I'll leave to you.
Also, the numbers in this paperwork need to be fixed.
The Student Council will probably just send it back if we don't.
Let's see, the Arabic numerals too, and here,
the calculations are wrong.
It's probably because of the mismatch here and the increase here.
This shift and the growth here are causing it.
I see.
I redid the calculations for the rest, but it was just this part so it's fine.
I don't think I should input it myself without permission,
so I just recompiled the files and the accurate figures.
If you enter this as is, it should be okay,
but you may want to recalculate it yourself, Sensei.
I sorted the rest into categories.
These just need looking over,
and these require entries.
I've filled in the simple parts here.
I've only entered sections I can fill out as your proxy,
so please be careful.
I've left notes for parts that need your input.
They're ordered by upcoming deadlines, but
there may be some with importance I can't grasp,
so I think you should look over these by the end of this week.
This is the only deadline this week.
That's about everything, I think.
I didn't see anything in particular I didn't understand after going through it all.
Let me know if anything seems off.
I-It's not like this is a big deal or anything.
It feels nice to be told that, but...
Um,
is there anything else I can help with?
Oh, I see.
So that stuff you were working on earlier...
You finished it without me noticing, huh?
That's good then.
What's wrong?
Y-You want praise?
I mean,
um,
what should I do?
Huh?
Oh,
never mind,
if that's good enough for Sensei.
Then...
Excuse me for a moment.
G-Good job...
I-Is this good enough?
I see.
But, certainly,
I know you've been working hard, Sensei.
Good work.
Somehow,
patting your head
feels a little embarrassing.
M-Me too?
Uh, um,
I-
It's okay.
For now,
I'm fine with it.
Transcribed using Whisper by OpenAI
Brought to you by nReus (via GitHub)