It's not getting done at all.
It's already this late.
I'm getting sleepy.
But no.
More...
Hm?
Oh!
S-Sensei.
W-What are you doing here?
We didn't have any appointments or meetings scheduled today.
Is there some business with the Prefect Team?
Y-Yeah.
N-No, it's fine.
It's no trouble at all.
You know...
Things got a bit hectic,
and I've been running around ever since.
I asked Ako and Iori to handle things outside.
Chinatsu's been working non-stop since yesterday,
so I had her go home around lunchtime.
Mm...
It's really okay.
I got the urgent stuff done for the most part.
But since the same thing could happen again,
I thought I should try to get some other work done if I can.
*sigh*
Hm?
My thigh.
Oh yeah.
I probably got grazed by a stray shot earlier when I was on backup.
It's fine, it doesn't hurt that much.
S-Sensei.
No, I'm okay.
You don't need to worry so much.
I have a pretty sturdy body.
It'll heal quickly if I just leave it alone.
Oh, well, if you say so...
It's not that big a deal if it leaves a mark.
Ah.
If you're going to insist,
then I'll leave it to you.
Let's see...
Then...
Right.
First aid kit.
Yeah, it's over there.
Then, um...
Please.
Ah.
Ow...
That's...
Let's see...
Ow, ah, it's okay.
It just soaked through a little.
Keep going.
Sensei, I didn't know you could do that.
Yeah.
My leg doesn't hurt anywhere in particular, but...
My ankle too, mmhmm.
If I had to say, it's just a light bruise on my thigh.
For this much, it's
Oh, I-I see.
Then...
Let's see, the tail-end was...
Oh yeah, inside that...
On the inner side.
Should I apply a little more there?
Yeah.
Ah, thank you.
[Because I'm] head prefect?
It's not that
I'm tired, but it's nothing unusual.
I see.
Yeah.
Then...
Let me at least check my temperature.
Ah, w-wait a minute.
I-It's okay.
You can put it in from here.
Somehow it's been a while since I've had my temperature taken like this.
Even if I had a fever, it's not like I could take time off,
so if I did have one,
it's better not to know.
Oh, right.
That's true.
Now, I'm fine.
Because...
36.7 degrees.
Almost normal.
Yeah.
I guess I really am just a little tired.
Other than that, nothing in particular...
Y-You don't have to go that far.
It's not like I'm broken down or anything.
I see.
Then...
Um, inside that,
th-that...
Could I have some of those?
Yeah, the cooling pads.
I was thinking of putting them over my eyes.
It's okay.
Probably...
I'm just sleepy.
I don't think there's any swelling.
Is there a mirror somewhere?
Sensei, you...
Y-Yeah.
Okay.
Done?
Yeah.
You're right, Chinatsu said the same thing I think.
In that case,
it's better not to cool it down.
Hot water?
Then, that faucet over there.
Ah, I'll do it.
Y-Yeah.
Okay, please.
Thank you
for the towel.
It's warm.
Should I just place this over my eyes?
Yeah.
Okay.
This really...
feels so nice.
Somehow...
today in particular,
I've done nothing but cause you trouble, Sensei.
It helps to hear you say that.
Hm?
That's...
um...
Lying down,
I feel like I might fall asleep like this.
I did get the necessary stuff done today, but...
Yeah.
This...
feels really nice, but...
I'm seriously
about to fall asleep.
It's warm.
Sensei.
So...
After a little while,
I'll wake up.
Until then...
Could you stay by my side...
until I open my eyes?
Thank you.
You really are...
so kind.
Hm?
Y-You've already
done more than enough
for me in so many ways
No one else has come yet, right?
Um...
before that,
when we get to Schale,
could you...
Thank you, Sensei.
*sigh*
Just a little longer
like this.
Transcribed using Whisper by OpenAI
Brought to you by nReus (via GitHub)