Sorry for the wait, Sensei.
Ah, no, you aren't. [*being a bother]
You don't have to look so worried.
At least you didn't get caught in the rain.
I'm guessing you were probably out enjoying some sweet treats somewhere.
A lot of the girls here don't like the rain.
Well, at least it wasn't a situation where you were stuck and couldn't leave.
You were eating the snacks I brought last time, so
it's not like you didn't come back at all.
Though constantly worrying about food
might not be the best approach.
Yeah, thank you.
That's right, she can be quite whimsical at times.
I'm sure she's fine, though.
I think she's capable of thinking for herself and moving freely.
Ah, this?
Just the trash from an empty can.
Since I was the one who brought it,
I couldn't just leave it lying around.
Ah, thank you. It's not heavy or anything.
Yeah, shall we get going then?
It doesn't look like the rain will stop anytime soon,
but there's no point in just waiting here,
I'm sure you have things to do, Sensei.
Come on, let's go, Sensei.
You're quite forgetful, aren't you, Sensei?
No, I don't mean there's something specific you've forgotten that I want you to remember.
I just feel like you forget your umbrella fairly often.
Or maybe you do it on purpose?
Sorry, don't worry about what I just said.
No, it's fine for me, but
this umbrella is quite large for a folding one.
Ah, I lent my spare umbrella to Mutsuki this morning.
Haruka is with the President, so she's probably okay.
Though the President might have forgotten hers.
Well, we have some extras at the office, so it'll be fine.
Um, what were we talking about again?
Ah, about you often forgetting your umbrella.
But now that I think about it,
before meeting me,
you might have lent your umbrella to another student,
so that could be the reason.
Well, the truth doesn't really matter.
By the way, do you have any plans today, Sensei?
No, I know you're busy, but
I was wondering if you had any fixed commitments after this.
I see.
No, it's just that I naturally started heading towards the Schale.
I was just wondering if it was okay for me to go there as well.
Well then, I'll join you.
It's fine. I've already informed the others.
Ah, a virtual umbrella?
Sorry, but I'll have to decline that.
If I lend you a virtual one, you'd definitely tip it to cover me more than yourself.
You know that. In fact, that's what happened last time, right?
There are a lot of students who would be troubled if you caught a cold.
So you need to take care of your health.
Especially since you're graciously keeping me company like this.
If you caught a cold after this, I'd feel really guilty.
Well, no, that's not quite what I meant.
It's not that I'd feel guilty, but rather,
I just don't want you to catch a cold.
Here, come a bit closer.
You'll get splashed if you stand too far.
It doesn't seem to be letting up at all.
In fact, it might be raining a little harder now.
Hm? The rain?
Oh.
Well, I wouldn't say I actively love it.
The splashing, the poor visibility, and so on.
There are girls who struggle to find shelter.
Getting soaked or dirty from the rain itself isn't a big deal for me.
But there are people who care about me now.
The President and Haruka would nag me about it,
telling me to change clothes immediately,
and desperately try to wash off any stains, even though detergent is scarce.
As for Mutsuki, well,
she seems to enjoy seeing me like that more than before.
As I mentioned earlier, they often forget umbrellas due to their scatterbrained nature.
Just the mention of rain can escalate into a huge fuss.
My point wandered a bit there.
Anyway, I don't dislike the rain as much as I used to.
Yeah, I don't dislike it.
That might be the closest way to express it.
And when it rains, though they get noisy, it also brings a sense of calm.
The sound of raindrops hitting umbrellas and the ground.
Being enveloped by those rhythmic yet random sounds,
it almost feels like the noise lessens,
allowing me to be still and ponder things.
Though with the usual noisy bunch around,
it's hard to have that experience.
Taking everything into account, I don't dislike the rain.
What about you, Sensei? Do you like the rain?
I figured you'd say that.
No, you don't need to give me a reason.
You'll probably just say something that confuses me anyway.
Here, come closer.
I told you, you'll get splashed if you stay far away.
Maybe even more so.