Sensei, I borrowed a towel.
Are there any towels I shouldn't borrow?
Is it okay to use any of them?
Okay, got it.
Ah, geez.
Here Sensei, wipe your head before dealing with the paperwork.
It'd be troublesome if you got it wet with water.
Stay still.
Sorry, you got pretty soaked.
Ah well, I didn't expect a tank to come rolling up right in front of Schale at the very end though.
It's my fault for not being able to protect you.
You were totally drenched.
Are you okay?
Ah, really?
Well, Haruka and the President often come back soaking wet.
And Mutsuki loves pulling silly stunts like this.
So in that sense, I might just be used to it by now.
Look down for me please.
Gently...
Well, I guess that's about it there.
Could you turn your head a bit to the left?
Ah, your ear is wet inside too. Hold still.
By the way, were you planning to work like that, Sensei?
Why don't you go change instead?
No, not air drying.
If you do that, you'll catch a cold for sure.
With how careless you are, I'm surprised you don't get sick more often.
Sensei, are you quite the lazy one?
Did you used to hide it better when we first met?
Well, I guess you're dry now at least.
But being slovenly isn't good.
I'm not saying you have to live completely neatly,
but if something is preventable, shouldn't you try to prevent it?
Well, considering how the Problem Solvers live,
it's not really my place to say that, is it?
Show me your other ear.
Hmm, looks okay.
Okay, turn the other way.
This side too...
Excuse me Sensei, could you wait a moment?
I'll borrow this.
Here, have a seat.
Yeah, this will be easier.
Alright, let me try again.
Ah, I just realized, whose turn is it for Schale duty today?
Hmm, I see.
Ah, no, nevermind.
I'm not really in a position to comment on that system.
Then I guess it worked out conveniently.
No, since I came by unexpectedly,
I thought it might be a bit awkward to cross paths
with whoever was actually on duty.
It saves me from having to worry about that.
All right, I think that's about it.
Your hair should be fine too?
It looks okay.
Ah, my bad.
Ah no, I kind of ended up petting your head there.
Ah, but it's weird for me to apologize too.
Don't worry about it.
Uh, don't you have work to do, Sensei?
Yeah, it's fine.
I came here on my own accord today after all.
Is there any work I can help out with?
I see.
Well, at least you're not swamped then.
If there's anything else you need help with besides work, I can do that.
Did you just start to say something and stop?
Cleaning is fine by me.
I don't mind tidying up.
No, you can see for yourself.
Before I could even think "there's nothing here",
your gaze went towards the back.
Not to mention, the state of this room...
What happened here?
A week...
Or maybe even a few weeks without cleaning, it seems.
Well, I guess it can end up like this if you've been away at a far school.
For now, I'll clean up while you work, Sensei.
I thought about using a vacuum,
but the condition of the place doesn't really allow for that right now.
Then... First I'll throw away the trash,
pick up the clothes for laundry, and dust things off.
And then...
I'll be washing clothes, but is there anything you don't want me touching?
Okay.
Then I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry, I won't throw anything away on my own.
I'll ask if I'm unsure.
Ah, but I can throw away those trash bags over there, right?
Understood.
Alright, let's get started then.
I'll take it all out to the hallway first.
Hmm, can't really wash this.
I'll just set it aside for now.
Should I just wash the inner clothes?
Here we go.
Let's see...
Okay.
I was thinking of taking everything out, but
Ah, don't worry about it.
I planned to dust from the top down, then do the floor,
but it might make the whole room dusty
while you're trying to work.
For today, I'll just tidy up and do some light cleaning.
Is it okay if I dust around your desk area?
Understood, got it.
Let me know if anything concerns you.
Alright...
Okay...
Heave-ho.
And...
This one too.
Hmm...
Hup.
There...
Now then.
Let's see...
Put this back.
And then the vacuum...
Found it.
Umm...
The switch is...
Yep.
This noise level should be fine.
Heave-ho.
Phew.
Next is...
Should I clean the path?
Gently.
I'll be vacuuming again.
What are you writing?
Umm...
And then...
That should be okay.
Huh, what's this?
Wow...
Ah!
You startled me.
Sorry, I didn't notice you there.
Oh, yeah.
I finished cleaning up.
Well, just this room, but still.
Should I clean the other rooms too?
You're right, it'd be neverending if I tried tackling everything.
I brought the clothes over to that area.
I washed what seemed okay and put that in the laundry.
For items that didn't seem machine-washable,
I just hung them up on hangers for now.
The copier was out of paper,
so I reloaded it from the spare stash.
The whiteboard markers and such,
and other consumables still seem fine.
It's nothing.
You don't need to thank me for it.
I'm the one imposing by staying here.
Oh, and this...
Did you get this recently?
Nice speaker system.
I'm not too savvy with equipment,
but it looks pretty good to me.
I can give it a try?
Ah, but I don't have any CDs with me right now.
Should I use one of yours, Sensei?
Oh, the one you mentioned before?
So you did end up getting it too, huh?
I see.
Then let's use that.
By the way Sensei,
have you reached a good stopping point with your work?
I see.
Good work.
Well, your work never really ends, does it?
But maybe you should take a little break.
Ah...
But if that's the case,
could you wait just a moment?