Thanks for the shower, Sensei.
Even though it wasn't a thorough cleaning, things still get a bit dusty after tidying up.
Yeah, it feels refreshing.
Oh, I also borrowed a hairdryer and an ear pick.
Yeah. Since we have such good audio equipment,
it's best to listen to the great sound it produces
in optimal conditions, right?
So hey, why don't you let me clean your ears too, Sensei?
Oh, no, I phrased that poorly.
No, it's fine if you don't want me to, but I don't mind doing it for you.
Alright then, I'll do it.
Um, how should we do this?
I guess you could lay a towel over my lap?
Nevermind, it's okay.
Let's just use that sofa.
Please, go ahead.
It feels a bit weird, doesn't it?
Well, seeing your face up this close is an unusual experience.
Ah, anyway I have the ear pick and cotton buds ready.
What?
Do you enjoy this intimidating look on my face?
Don't say anything weird, I might slip up.
Actually, I can't clean your ears if you're looking up,
so could you turn your head and face that way instead?
Okay, shall we begin?
I'll be gentle, but let me know if it hurts at all.
It might tickle, so try not to move too much.
It's pretty clean, so I don't need to dig too hard.
Let me start with the outer grooves first,
slowly and carefully.
Scritch, scritch.
How's that?
No pain or weird sensations?
Good, I'm glad.
Okay, going a bit deeper now.
If you feel like sneezing or moving, let me know right away.
Cleaning like this.
Trying not to scrape the inner walls too much,
don't want to irritate the membranes.
I won't go too deep since earwax naturally comes out on its own.
Besides, it serves a protective function in moderation.
So I'll be careful not to disrupt that process too much.
Alright, I think that ear is clean now.
How does it feel? Any weird sensations or problem areas?
If it's all good, I'll use the cotton buds to finish up.
Okay, here goes.
Hm? No, it's nothing.
Well, Mutsuki and the others act silly and clingy sometimes, so I guess during moments like that.
With the President and Haruka though...
I mean, they might tease me after seeing me do this for Mutsuki,
but I don't really do it for them.
So I'm just used to it, I guess.
Right now I'm just being careful, that's probably why it seems that way.
The feeling?
Well, that's good then.
They say there's something called the vagus nerve.
Stimulating that area can induce pleasurable sensations.
For some people it might even trigger coughing reflex.
Since it involves nerve stimulation, you don't want to overdo it of course.
But a little bit more won't hurt.
Okay, looks good.
Oh, are you alright?
Just startled?
Sorry, I should have warned you first.
What's wrong?
If you're okay then.
Let me try again.
There, that side is done.
Could you turn the other way?
Really, it's fine.
Your face is flushed though, Sensei.
Nevermind that.
Okay, I'm inserting the pick again, so stay still.
Need to get this ear just as clean as the other.
Calling it purification might be going overboard,
but don't you have rituals like that, Sensei?
Like when you get a new CD you've been anticipating,
you clean your room, take a shower,
and get everything ready before really sitting down to enjoy it?
Video games?
Ah, I see.
Well, I don't play much, but it's a similar feeling.
Music is mainly experienced through the ears,
so you want them to be clean, makes sense.
Not that you need me to explain, but
basically, sound works by the eardrum sensing air vibrations in the inner ear,
which has an intricate structure,
evolved to capture all the nuances artists labor over
when creating their work through constant refinement.
And audio equipment goes through similar iteration
to reproduce that sound
as faithfully as possible.
So in a way, maintaining good listening conditions
is just part of making an effort to properly appreciate the art.
More of a mindset than pragmatic necessity, I suppose.
But one I try to uphold nonetheless.
Ah, sorry for rambling.
My apologies, I tend to go on about this stuff.
Um...
Okay, looking good.
Now for the cotton buds.
This side okay too? Not ticklish?
Good, that's a relief.
I suppose so.
Well, rambling isn't exactly my strong suit, but I do tend to go into detail.
There are enough chatterboxes in our group as is.
Yeah, I may not be an expert, but I do enjoy learning about audio gear
and the technical side of music production. Comes with the territory, I guess.
Though I doubt my knowledge goes much deeper than any other enthusiast's.
No need for compliments, really.
Even with our...lifestyle choices,
we all study plenty hard when it counts.
The President was getting tutoring from you recently, right Sensei?
Though she'd rather focus on business management and such.
Mutsuki could ace everything if she applied herself instead of wasting time.
Haruka is knowledgeable about botany and the like too.
If you're interested, maybe you could teach a class for us four?
No pressure of course.
We know you're busy, I'm just suggesting it casually.
Don't worry about it.
I got sidetracked there for a bit,
but I've been focused this whole time, promise.
Scritch, scritch, scritch.
Okay, I think we got all the wax out.
Right, then.
Actually, am I being too rough?
But it you don't seem to be in pain, so I'll keep at it gently.
Just try not to move too suddenly, you'll startle me.
I think we're good to go.
Both ears seem nice and clean now. How do they feel?
No weird sensations or pain anywhere?
That's a relief then.
Don't worry about it.
Just my way of returning the many favors.