Good morning!
It's hot again today, isn't it?
Yes,
I've waited a little while.
Let's see...
About 30 minutes, I think?
You kept the promised time, so there's no need to apologize.
I was just so looking forward to our date that I ended up arriving earlier than scheduled.
Besides, it's not like I was bored while waiting.
Yes.
Just thinking about you while I waited made my heart pound and filled me with excitement.
Oh?
Your face is red. Is something wrong?
Could it be that you're embarrassed?
Oh? Well, if it's nothing, then it's fine.
By the way, you look like you want to say something. What is it?
Is something wrong with this outfit?
I bought it just for today, but... maybe it's too childish?
C-Cute? You think it's cute?
Hearing you say that makes me a little embarrassed.
But I'm happy. Thank you.
Also, your clothes look really good on you too.
It's a nice look.
It's wonderful.
Right then. Shall we get going?
But, before that... my hand feels kind of lonely.
My hand might get cold if I leave it like this.
Mhm.
This way, my hand won't get cold, it seems.
How many times does this make that we've held hands?
Even though this isn't the first time, my heart always pounds.
What about you?
How do you feel?
I see. The same as me.
Well then, let's go.
It looks like today will be a fun day.