Today was fun, wasn't it?
Riding various attractions, enjoying delicious sweets...
Oh, right, we bought lots of souvenirs too.
Raisin butter, bitter chocolate, caramel popcorn...
I bought them thinking they'd be snacks to go with drinks, but I wonder if my sister will like them.
True, it's all sweets, but my sister snacks on sweets while drinking, so that part should be fine. No need to worry.
Right. Like you said, she'll probably complain that the essential drinks are missing.
But they didn't sell alcohol, so she'll have to make do with these.
Even so, today was truly a wonderful day.
It's been a long time since I had such a fun day.
Let's come back to Sweets Island together again sometime.
Yes, it's a promise. Oh, right, let's do a pinky swear.
No? You can't keep the promise?
In that case, let's do a pinky swear.
Okay then.
Pinky swear, made a promise. If you tell a lie, swallow a thousand needles. Pinky promise sealed.
Now, if you break this promise, I won't forgive you.
Well then, my house is that way, so let's part ways here.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
What's wrong?
You seem fidgety. Is there something you want to say?
It's nothing?
But you've been glancing at my face since a moment ago.
Is there something on my lips?
Just blushing doesn't tell me anything.
If you have something to say, please say it clearly.
Since you're silent, I'll interpret that as there being nothing in particular. Is that okay with you?
I see. In that case, I'll be heading home.
Oh, right, right.
Speaking of which, I forgot I had a souvenir for you.
I made sure to get one for you too.
I'll give it to you now, but I want to surprise you, so could you close your eyes?
Yes, just like that. Stay still.
This is your souvenir.
Well then, good night.