I'm sorry.
I was so focused on the sweets that I only picked intense attractions...
And because of that, you ended up feeling unwell...
So...
I'm truly sorry.
Ah!
Don't move.
You should rest a little longer.
Don't push yourself.
Oh, I know.
Shall I go get you a cold drink or something?
Is just having me nearby enough?
Is there anything else you'd like me to do?
A lap pillow?
You want me to give you a lap pillow?
Of course, that's fine. If my lap is okay, please, go ahead.
Nh.
How are you feeling?
I see.
That's good.
So, what should we do after this?
Somewhere you want to go?
Let me see...
If it's okay with you, I'd like to try riding the Ferris wheel.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
Well then, after you rest a bit more, let's ride the Ferris wheel.
The view is beautiful!
Look, you can see the whole park!
The view from the sky feels so nice, doesn't it?
Don't you think so too?
I'm more beautiful than the view?
Since when did you become such a smooth talker?
But, if you're feeling like that, it seems your condition isn't a problem anymore.
That's good.
Alright then, let's have the limited-edition sweet, the baked apple cream puff.
The nice thing about the Ferris wheel is that you can enjoy sweets while riding the attraction.
Well then...
Mmm...
The pastry is crisp and fragrant, and the tartness of the apple perfectly matches the sweetness of the cream...
Ah?
Why the sudden strange face? What's wrong?
Behind me?
What's behind me?
Huh? A bug?!
It came this way?! Aah!
I'm sorry, suddenly shouting like that...
It just happened so suddenly, I was startled.
My heart is still pounding.
Huh?
You can feel my heartbeat directly?
Ah!
Um...
Well...
Sorry for the commotion.
I'm sorry for suddenly clinging to you like that.
I must have bothered you.
A perk?
Well then, maybe I should cling to you one more time?
Hehe.
Just kidding.
Okay then, let's eat the rest of the cream puff...
Oh?
During that commotion, some cream got on you.
Mm-hmm, it's on the other side.
No, not there...
Hold still for a moment, would you?
It's alright, just hold still, okay? Got it?
*lick*
There. It's off.
Since it was just the two of us, I licked it off without thinking, but...
Was that a little ill-mannered?
Hehe.