Which attraction should we go to first?
Big Parfait Mountain...
Marshmallow Tours...
Milky World...
There are so many, it's hard to decide, isn't it?
Hmm, let's see...
How about this Chocolate Splash?
You ride a boat down the river and experience the story of the little people who make chocolate.
That sounds quite interesting, doesn't it?
I wonder if it ends with falling down a waterfall?
Hey, what do you think?
Oh?
That look on your face... maybe you're not good with this kind of thing?
Are you really okay?
I see. In that case, Chocolate Splash should be fine, right?
Let's go.
Phew.
The end was surprising, but it was quite fun.
Ah.
It looks like the photos from the moment we dropped are displayed on that monitor over there.
I wonder how we look in them.
Let's go see.
Um...
Our photo is...
Found it! That's the one.
You're making quite a face!
So you really didn't like it, huh?
Huh?
I clung onto you?
Why would you say such nonsense?
Certainly, in the monitor, it looks like I'm clinging to you, but that's wrong.
You were the one clinging.
Do you have any objections?
Well, if there's nothing else, let's end this discussion and go eat the limited-edition sweets.
Um, it looks like we pick up the sweets at that counter over there and eat them at the tables further back.
Alright then, let's go buy them right away!
So these truffle chocolates are the limited-edition sweets you can buy at Chocolate Splash.
Wow! They're beautiful, like candy sculptures.
And they smell so good... Mmm... They look incredibly delicious.
Well then, time to try them.
Ooh.
Mmm.
Delicious!
Wonderful! Excellent! This chocolate is a perfect 100 out of 100!
The chocolate melts smoothly on my tongue, and the deep flavor of cacao gently spreads through my mouth...
I can't take it anymore... It's so delicious, I feel like I'm going to melt too...
Haaa...
I want to bask in this sweet afterglow forever...
Ah.
Ex-Excuse me.
I got carried away again, didn't I?
It was just so delicious that I couldn't help it...
Please, don't say anything.
If you say something now, I'll get really embarrassed.
Even so, Sweets Island is a wonderful place, isn't it?
Not only are the attractions fun, but to think we can eat such delicious sweets!
Nom.
Ahh.
I'm so happy, I feel like I could lose my mind.
I'm really glad we came to Sweets Island.
What is it? Staring at my face like that.
Is there something on it?
Huh?
The reason I hadn't been to Sweets Island until now?
Well, it's partly that I didn't have the chance, but...
I had decided that my first time at Sweets Island would be with someone I like.
That's the reason.
Hehe.
Well then, let's head to the next attraction soon.
Next, is Big Parfait Mountain okay?
It's decided then.
Alright then, let's go quickly! We've got no time to waste!