Wow!
This is Sweets Island, the place I've only dreamed of!
I've wanted to come here for so long, and now my dream is finally coming true.
I'm sure I'll never forget this wonderful day.
What's wrong? You're spacing out.
Huh?
You don't know about Sweets Island?
Sweets Island, just like the name suggests, is an amusement park themed around sweets!
A spinning swing ride shaped like donuts,
a merry-go-round shaped like a cake, a Ferris wheel shaped like cream puffs...
There are attractions modeled after various sweets.
It's full of dreams and playfulness, isn't it interesting?
Also, there's a special service unique to Sweets Island that other amusement parks don't have.
After enjoying an attraction, you get to taste sweets!
For example, if you ride the donut-shaped spinning swing, you can buy donuts afterward.
For the merry-go-round, it's cake. For the Ferris wheel, it's cream puffs.
Just like that, various sweets are prepared for each attraction.
And what's more, they aren't just any sweets!
Raw(?) donuts with dutch(?)berry sauce,
White chocolate Sachertorte, baked apple cream puffs...
Each and every one is a limited-edition sweet that you can only taste at Sweets Island!
Limited-edition sweets... What a wonderful sound.
My dreams are expanding!
I wonder what they taste like?
The pamphlet says they are gentle-tasting sweets made with the best ingredients... Just imagining it makes my heart flutter!
Oh?
Why are you chuckling?
"So earnest," you say...
Am I getting too carried away?
I was really looking forward to today, so I guess I got a bit lost in the moment.
It's kind of embarrassing.
You think I'm cute?
Hearing you say that makes me even more embarrassed.
But... hearing that from someone I like makes me really happy after all.
Well then, shall we go check out the attractions?
You're right. Since there are a lot of people, it looks like we'll have to wait for a long time.
Sweets Island has been super popular ever since it opened, and depending on the attraction, I think we'll have to wait quite a bit.
Are you bad at waiting?
Yeah, I know. There aren't many people who like waiting, right?
But, I'm relatively okay with it.
Like I said earlier, while waiting, you can have fun imagining various things, right?
Also, while waiting, sometimes they give out samples of the limited-edition sweets.
If we chat while eating those, the waiting time will fly by!
Come on, let's go!