Ao no Kanata no Four Rhythm
Misaki's Lovey-Dovey Diary - Part 1
Okay, the fluorescent light's cord is first buoy,
this spot on the bookshelf is second buoy,
the closet handle is third buoy, and the stain on the wall is fourth buoy.
And with that, a field has been born in my room!
So, this Shito-kun I'm holding in my right hand is me, and the Shito-kun in my left hand is him.
With that setup, let the practice match begin!
To develop my FC head, daily training is necessary, you know!
Practicing hard in my room even after regular practice... that's our admirable Misaki-chan!
By repeatedly playing matches on this indoor field, I'll aim to become the world's greatest brainy Sky Walker!
I won't let anyone say I just fly by intuition anymore!
Let's do this! Yeah!
Go for it, me!
Well, it's a bit late to bring this up now, but...
Shito-kun really has a weird face...
No wonder so many islanders said they found it physiologically unacceptable. I get it.
Substituting ourselves with these...
Yeah, I have some reservations about it.
Hmm.
But hey, if I get used to it, even Shito-kun will start looking cute!
It takes quite... well...
Umm, depending on my effort, depending on how hard I try, I can just barely manage to see it as cute!
Besides, this is a precious stuffed toy he won for me in a crane game at the arcade.
Hrmmm...
Focus, focus.
It looks cute, it looks cute, it looks cute, it looks cute...
Mmm, yaah!
I see it! I can see it!
It looked cute! Shito-kun is cute!
Right then, I'll put my soul into the right-hand Shito-kun.
Alright, it's in!
And then, I'll arbitrarily put his soul into the left-hand Shito-kun.
It's in!
There we go.
Okay, now we can start the practice match!
Alright, let's have a match today too!
First, wait at the fluorescent light cord's first buoy.
Hello, Misaki.
Let's have a good match today.
Likewise! Let's do our best, Darling.
Alright then, before the match starts...
Wh-What are you doing all of a sudden?
There's no rule saying you can't kiss before a match, right?
W-Well, maybe there isn't a rule like that, but it's bad manners! That!
My bad.
Well then, shall we start the match?
What are you doing?
Counter-attack!
If someone suddenly kisses you, isn't it good manners to return the sudden kiss?
Which means, I have to kiss you next.
But if we do that, the kissing will never end.
That's exactly what I want! The first one to stop loses, you know!
Hey, am I an idiot?!
What on earth am I doing, squishing stuffed animals together?!
Ah!
I slammed the Shito-kun with my and his souls against the wall!
I did such a terrible thing...
Haaah.
I know I need to take this seriously, but...
Oof.
Even while thinking that, I end up lying down on the bed. That's me.
Haaah.
Somehow, I'm just not in the mood.
Today's practice was pretty hard, so maybe I'm just tired.
Haaah.
Haaaaah.
Aaaah.
Aaaah... aaaah...
I'll do my best-zoi.
Hm.
Haaah.
He looked cool during practice today, too.
I wonder what he's doing right now.
Mmm.
Is he thinking about me, even a little?
I'm his girlfriend, so of course he is, right?
Or is he thinking about some other girl?
No, he's a coach, so even if he *is* thinking about another girl...
Well, that's to be expected, but...
The Shito-kun imbued with his soul is... over there, huh.
Hello? This is Misaki.
Can you hear me through Shito-kun?
Please respond.
Hellooo?
Wait,
if it actually responded and Shito-kun started talking, like some occult phenomenon...
I'd immediately throw Shito-kun out the window, but...
Putting that aside, I'm just thinking I'd like to hear his voice.
I could probably tolerate a small occult phenomenon.
Maybe I'll try giving it a big squee~eze hug like this.
Doing something really girly like this...
Getting weirdly flustered...
It'd be pretty scary if I heard a voice, but just feeling his warmth might be kind of girly-cute, maybe.
No, that's still scary.
A lukewarm Shito-kun is pure horror.
A purification ritual at a temple would be mandatory.
Aah.
Mmmm.
Haaah.
I don't mind if it's an occult phenomenon, I just want to hear his voice, and...
just for a little bit, I want to feel some warmth.
Hello? Please answer me.
I'm thinking of you so desperately, you know?
If only these feelings could ride on some suspicious radio waves and reach him...
Isn't there a machine for that?
Haaah.
It would be nice if there was a convenient machine to deliver my voice to him.
Huh?
Ah.
There is!
It was right in front of me!
You mean a phone!
Civilization is amazing!
Um, who invented the telephone again?
Umm, Bell?
Yeah, pretty sure it was Bell.
You're brilliant, Bell! Woo! *clap clap clap*
Lying around like this, thinking dangerously girly thoughts, isn't like me.
My style is being a fighter!
I attack! I attack with my cell phone!
Ah.
But warmth doesn't travel through a cell phone, huh.
Hmm, civilization isn't that amazing after all.
It needs to do better.
I think it could if it tried.
Why doesn't it take things seriously?
Mmm.
Just hearing his voice feels kinda boring.
I want more, like...
hugging tightly, or being hugged tightly...
That's what I want.
Mmmm.
Ah, geez!
What should I do about this frustration?
His girlfriend is feeling gloomy, so I wish he'd use psychic powers to sense it and rush over.
I think it's okay for a boyfriend to do that much.
Is there some way... huh?
I didn't need to worry about that!
I didn't need psychic powers either!
Um, first, I make a call,
Yep.
Answer... answer... He answered!
Hello? Your cute girlfriend is coming over to see you right now, so make sure you're fully prepared for hugs and waiting!
Hmph!
There, that's settled.
Alright Shito-kun, hold down the fort, okay?
I'll practice properly when I get back, so wait for me!
Yahooey!