Ao no Kanata no Four Rhythm
Misaki's Lovey-Dovey Diary - Part 2
Because I feel like teasing you!
Don't look at me with that "What are you talking about?" face.
It's fine, it's fine. Being teased by your cute girlfriend is a boyfriend's privilege, you know.
Everyone will be so jealous.
Okay, time to explain the rules.
If you make a sound before I say "stop," you have to treat me to a parfait.
After eating something sweet, I'll want something salty too, so you can add udon to that if you want.
If you endure until the very end?
Hmm.
Let's see.
Uhh, how about... you can do whatever you want with me?
Because I'm confident, you see!
It's okay to say something like this.
Well then, that's how it is.
Now then, what should I do first?
I have various plans, you know.
First, I'll boldly use the forbidden raw beef liver I carelessly left in my bag...
Of course that's a lie!
A girl who keeps raw liver in a normal bag like this?
Or rather, I don't think many humans like that exist.
Actually, it's... a cockroach.
I'll slip this down your back.
I told you, it's a joke!
I just thought of teasing you now, so there's no way I'd have prepared such a convenient item beforehand!
Ahh.
Were you perhaps hoping for something naughty?
Is that what you like? I wonder?
Hey, hey, hey, what about it? Are you hoping for it?
Hey, hey, hey.
Answer me!
I thought you'd easily open your mouth to answer the question here, but I guess you didn't fall for it.
So, are you hoping your mean girlfriend will do things like that to you?
Hey, what about it?
I know you are. That's it, right?
Do you want me to do naughty, mean things to you?
But you know, when you expect things like that, it makes me want to do the opposite.
Got it? You absolutely cannot open your mouth, okay?
Understand?
I'll check again and again, but if you open it, you lose, okay?
You understand, right?
Komanechi!
Nejikoma?
You're surprisingly resilient, nya.
Having corny jokes thrown at you when you're not supposed to laugh must be pretty tough, I think.
However, the real show starts now.
Get ready, because Misaki-chan's 100 Gag Barrage is about to begin!
Can you withstand the corniest jokes from all times and places?
Or so I'd make you think...
Squeeze!
How's that?
Being hugged head-on, you should be thinking how amazing a girl's body is.
It's soft and feels good, right?
Rub rub rub rub rub.
Since I'm pressing myself against you so tightly like this, I think you could shout for joy and pass out.
Look, look, I'll even rub my cheek against yours, nya.
Mmmm.
Nyaaan, nyaaan.
Nyaaan, rub rub rub.
Nyaaan.
My cheek is so smooth, nyaaan.
I even used a purring voice and staged a sudden climax, but you won't even let out a moan? I really don't get it.
If that's how you want to play it, I have my own ideas.
Your girlfriend is nibbling on your earlobe, and you won't even make a sound? How rude!
At least twitch like you've been zapped with electricity!
Letting your girlfriend do this to you and acting all nonchalant... isn't that reaching the level of being impolite?
If it's come to this, I'll definitely make you feel good!
How is it? Ticklish but feels good, right?
Come to think of it, I didn't even know ears felt this good until it happened to me.
I mean, I never really imagined people doing things like this to each other.
The human body is strange, isn't it? What's the point of having such sensitive spots here?
Putting those questions aside... I'll return the favor for all the times you made me feel good.
Maybe I'll even use my tongue...
Hmm? It should feel really good, but you're holding back.
N-No way! How could this be!
Not making a sound even after this... my pride as your girlfriend has been deeply wounded!
If the roles were reversed, I definitely wouldn't be able to stand it!
Mmm, well then, I still have this method!
Getting behind you...
How about this!
Squeeze.
I wrapped my arms tightly around you and pressed myself right against your back.
Focus your senses on your back and think very carefully about what this means.
Hmph.
Come on, come on, feel me properly.
Oh? Good reaction.
You just twitched, didn't you?
The thing you love most is pressed right against your back.
Come on, come on, isn't this a big deal?
Wow, how bold. I'm being very bold.
I'm squished against your back.
How is it? This should make you make a sound, right?
Geez! Are you still holding back?
Unbelievable. Get more serious about this.
Normally, you'd make a sound. I mean, look, we're this close!
Having a girl do this to you and still managing to hold back your voice...
Unforgivable!
Grr!
Komanechi!
So close! You almost burst out laughing just now, didn't you?
Just one more step!
Haaah.
If you had just made a sound somewhere along the line, I would have let you off with just the parfait.
It seems you really want me to tease you seriously.
I didn't know you had such strong masochistic desires.
Right, I've grabbed both your wrists.
What shall I do with these hands?
Hehe.
You thought I'd bring them to my chest, didn't you?
No, no, no.
I wouldn't do something so simple, nya.
Hands are very sensitive places, so...
You didn't expect to be kissed on the hand, did you?
I'm going to make this a place that feels good, okay?
Since your ears feel so good, I bet it'll feel really good if I do it to your hands.
Ah.
You're hoping for it.
Making a face like that... are you embarrassed?
Your heart's pounding, isn't it?
Getting teased by your girlfriend is making your heart pound, isn't it?
Well, maybe my heart's pounding a little too.
Well then...
How was it? If it felt good, nod your head yes.
Hmm, I see. Naughty.
Making such a naughty face from something like this... you really are naughty.
Not just with my lips, I'll use my tongue too.
I'll lick your fingers.
How is it? If it felt good, nod.
Geez, nodding your head yes so many times. You Komanechi!
Huh?
Too resilient.
I really thought this surprise attack would work...
Alright then, the standard approach.
How's that? Aren't your hands getting more and more sensitive?
I absolutely won't hold back here.
I'm going to take your finger deep into my mouth. Mmm, mhm, mhm. Fumuke(?).
You're starting to want to make a sound, aren't you?
Huh?
I'll take it deep, so you can move your finger inside my mouth if you want.
Ah...
Ah, I'm starting to feel kinda dazed.
You can stir things up inside my mouth more, make it all messy...
Ah!
Did I just get carried away and do something crazy?
My head got a little hot for a moment.
I overdid it. I didn't mean to go this far.
It's true! This is definitely too much.
H-Hey, let's calm down a bit.
Yeah, let's calm down. I definitely feel like I overdid it.
Deep breath.
Right.
Haa.
S-So, anyway, let's just say this is the end for now.
Eh?
Bu-
Y...
You surprised me!
Wh-Why did you suddenly kiss me?
Eh? Oh?
Well, it's true you didn't open your mouth until I said stop, but...
Eh?
Ah, w-well, I certainly did say if you won, you could do what you want with me, but...
That was just said in the heat of the moment, I didn't really mean... Ah, y-you mean it?
Uh, um, maybe I should just confirm this, but...
Are you... going to do whatever you want with me now?
D-Don't just nod so firmly with a straight face and without a word!
Um...
Ehehehe...
K-Komanechi?
Yes! You just laughed a little! You laughed, right? My comeback victory!
Wah!
I-I got pushed down!
Ah...
Y-You kissed me again...
H-Hey, I was just kidding...
Huh? Wait, huh?
Isn't this weird? Why am I the one receiving?
I was supposed to be the one teasing...
Mmm... Ah... Hah...
N-No! If you kiss me like that, I'll get carried away!
Eh?
W-Well, it's not like I mind getting carried away, but...
B-But it's not like that! It's totally not like that!
It's because I like you! Because I like you, I'm *letting* myself get carried away on purpose, okay?!
Don't get the wrong idea about that!
Eh?
S-So, um...
Because I like you, I'll let you do what you want! That's what it means!
Ah...
L-Like! I love you!
S-So, isn't that obvious?!
So, from now on too...
Let's tease each other, okay?
Ehehe.
So, look, I want you to kiss me more...
A-After that's done, I-I'll accept... everything, so...
Let's kiss one more time.
Okay?
Because I like you...
It's okay, right?