Nii-san, it's hot! It's a tropical night! (t/n: Temp doesn't go below 20°C at night.)
Haa.
Huh? You say it can't be helped because it's the peak of summer?
But Nii-san, you keep saying things like "energy saving" and won't lower the AC temperature.
I don't think you'd be cursed if you made it just a little cooler.
Ahh, if this keeps up, I'll have no choice but to take off my clothes and spend the time naked!
You're okay with that?
N-Nii-san, you pervert! There's no way I can do that!
Hmm. If it's come to this,
Nii-san, let's bet the AC remote and have a match in a versus game!
If I win, you have to lower the AC temperature by 1 degree.
In return, if I lose, I'll take off one piece of clothing for you.
Nii-san, prepare yourself! I absolutely won't lose!
I'll keep lowering the AC temperature until you say it's cold, Nii-san!
Round 1, start!
Ugh, I lost to Nii-san...!
But...
I didn't lose because of my skill.
I lost to Nii-san's sly sexual harassment!
"Even so, a loss is a loss?"
Grrr, I know! I'll take off my clothes as promised!
So, with that, here, I took off my hair ornament.
Huh? Dirty trick? It doesn't count as taking off clothes?
That's not true!
Anyway, next match!
I won't lose this time!
Round 2, start!
Ughhhh, I lost to Nii-san again...
Ugh, I know. I just have to take off another piece of clothing, right?
So, with that, heave-ho, heave-ho.
Okay, I took off my socks.
Why do you look so dissatisfied? It's more decent than a hair ornament, right?
Besides, if I lose next time, I'll really have no choice but to take off proper clothes.
I absolutely won't lose!
This time for sure, I'll beat Nii-san!
Round 3, start!
Ughhhh, I still lost.
I lost to Nii-san's sly sexual harassment.
I know. A loss is a loss. I'll take them off properly.
Okay, I took off my sweater.
My upper body is just in a bra.
Ugh, it's embarrassing. Don't look too much.
More importantly, the next match!
I absolutely, absolutely won't lose!
Round 4, start!
Uwaah! I loooost again! And it was almost an instant kill!
Nii-san, I feel like you're getting stronger every time I take something off.
I know! I'll take it off properly! Next, I'll take off my skirt!
Okay, I took it off.
I'm... in my underwear, top and bottom.
N-No! Don't look! It's embarrassing. It's too embarrassing, I can't stand it!
I really can't lose anymore. No matter what, I can't lose!
Because, next time I take something off, it'll be my underwear!
That's absolutely not okay!
Nii-san, it's a match!
Round 5, start!
Aah, I lost.
Playing a game in my underwear... it's too embarrassing, I can't play properly!
Nii-san, you idiot! This is a dirty trick!
Y...Yeah, a loss is a loss.
I'll... obey Nii-san.
Well then, I'll take off my bra.
It's so embarrassing, I'm already out of breath.
Okay, I took off my bra.
Ahh, my boobs... Nii-san is looking at them.
He's even looking straight at my nipples.
But I'm not naked yet!
I still have my panties on!
I... I can still have a match with Nii-san!
I'll win next time for sure! I'll definitely beat Nii-san!
Round 6, start!
Noooo! I lost!
It's embarrassing, so embarrassing, I can't play properly at all!
Nii-san, were you aiming for this from the start?
Nii-san, you idiot! Pervert! Utter pervert! Super ultra pervert!
A match is a match.
I'll obey properly.
I'll... take everything off. I'll take off my panties too.
I took them off.
I... took everything off.
I'm... completely naked now.
I'm in my birthday suit in front of Nii-san.
Nii-san is seeing all my embarrassing parts.
My most embarrassing parts, even my precious parts... he saw them.
But I... I haven't lost yet!
I can't take anything else off, but if that's the case, I just need to set up a different penalty game!
Nii-san,
If you beat me,
You can do lewd things to me.
You can touch my lewd parts.
You can do anything to my naked body,
Anything to my precious parts.
It can't be helped.
To beat Nii-san, it can't be helped.
It's not like I particularly want Nii-san to do lewd things to me.
So, Nii-san,
Let's have more matches!
Round 7, start!
Mhm.
Lots and lots more starts!
The more you beat me, Nii-san, the more lewd things you can do.
I'll... keep playing with Nii-san until you're satisfied.
I'll play a lewd match with you.
Really, you're a hopeless Nii-san.
A perverted, silently lecherous Nii-san.
For such a Nii-san, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best as your little sister.
I'll play games with Nii-san naked, and I'll even submit to lewd penalty games.
Well then, let the match begin.
Lots and lots of beginnings!
Nii-san,
Be gentle, okay?
Huh?
Sometime before I knew it, it became morning.
I... fell asleep?
Nii-san is also sleeping while holding me.
We're... holding each other naked.
I... had Nii-san do lewd things to me...
Every time I lost a game he did lewd things to me...
He did lewd things to me tens of times,
And because of that, it felt so good, too good that maybe I lost consciousness.
Geez, Nii-san, you really are a pervert. A siscon pervert.
Thanks to that, even if I take off my clothes, it's still hot.
Even if I get naked, it's still hot.
When I'm like this with Nii-san, it's so incredibly hot.
But... I love this warmth.
I... love Nii-san very much.
If Nii-san were awake, I wouldn't say such things, though.
But Nii-san is still sleeping.
So let me say it now, while I can.
Nii-san, I like you. I really like you.
I love you.
I love you more than anyone in the world, Nii-san.