Koi to Senkyo to Chocolate, Drama CD
Watch out, Hazuki-sensei!
[PAUSE]
Yoo-hoo! Yuu-kun!
Pardon the intrusion~!
It's Shinonome Hazuki!
Ahahaha!
Hmm? I just happened to be in the neighborhood,
So I thought I'd drop by to see my beloved Yuu-kun's face!
Oh, was that not okay?
Well, you know...
Between you and me, Yuu-kun,
There's nothing off-limits anymore, right?
Oh?
Oh my, oh my?
Oh my, my, my, my, my!
sniff sniff sniff sniff
What's that delicious smell?
Could it be...
I think I know what it is!
Oh, my feet are moving on their own, taking me into Yuu-kun's house!
Oh, my feet, they're moving by themselves!
Ahahahaha!
Wobble, wobble, wobble...
Oops...
But first, I should take off my shoes.
Huh? Ehehe...
My hands are moving on their own too, somehow.
But my feet are also moving on their own to take off my shoes.
Hahahahaha!
That was close.
Thank you, Yuu-kun.
I almost bumped my forehead against the wall.
You're always so reliable, aren't you?
I'm fine, really.
I've had a bit to drink, but I'm not that drunk.
I'm just a little tipsy, that's all.
I'm telling you, I'm okay!
My liver is eleven times stronger than normal.
I could keep drinking way more!
Hahahaha!
Well then,
I guess I'll be making my way in now.
Huh?
You're saying it's not good...
For a teacher to visit a student's house privately?
It's fine, it's fine! Love conquers all, right?
Yuu-kun's house...
Uhuhu, it smells just like Yuu-kun!
Oh my, oh my! There's such delicious-looking food on the table!
Mmm~
Not only does it smell good, but the colors are balanced too - red, yellow, green...
It looks so nutritious, just like Yuu-kun's cooking should be.
Hey, hey, Yuu-kun, isn't there any for me?
Let me have some of Yuu-kun's cooking too!
I want to eat Yuu-kun's food... Hey, hey, come on!
Aww, I can't?
Yuu-kun's cooking...
You won't let me eat any of it?
Yuu-kun, you're so kind!
I love you so much!
Ahaha,
Too bad, you're right. I was fake crying.
But, but, I love how Yuu-kun responds so seriously to my silly little lies.
Ahaha!
Well then,
I'll just sit myself down right here~
Come on, Yuu-kun, sit down too! Hurry, hurry!
Yuu-kun, here. Aah~
What's the matter?
There's nothing wrong with a woman being a little spoiled, is there?
So come on,
Aah~
Delicious!
Yuu-kun's fried shrimp!
The breading is so crispy, and the shrimp is so juicy.
It's a perfect harmony in my mouth!
Mmm~ This fried rice is great too.
The rice is perfectly separated,
And the amount of egg is just right. I can't even describe it!
Marvelous!
Yuu-kun's cooking is really the best.
Oh? Oh my, oh my!
I just realized something terrible!
What should I do, what should I do, what should I do?
What, you ask?
Fufu~
What do you think it is, Yuu-kun?
I see, you can't imagine what it could be.
It's about your mother, Yuu-kun.
I wonder if she's home right now.
I see.
That was close.
She's not coming home today, huh?
Wait...
Eh?
She's not coming home?
Well, well, did you hear that, ladies and gentlemen?!
Yuu-kun's mother isn't coming home today!
My, my, I've certainly come at the perfect time, haven't I?
Yuu-kun, you were expecting this, weren't you?
Don't try to lie, it won't work.
Hazuki-sensei can see right through you, you know.
Why? Well, because I'm your beloved girlfriend, of course.
Let me ask you this, what do you think, Yuu-kun?
Do you think I'm not expecting anything?
Do I look like I'm not expecting anything?
That's right~ Fufu.
I'm just being honest,
And I certainly can't lie to you, Yuu-kun.
I'm in such a happy mood.
Besides, alcohol goes so well with Yuu-kun's cooking,
I think I'll have some more!
Phew!
Wow! I feel alive again!
Why is alcohol so delicious, I wonder?
I feel like I'm floating on a cloud, drifting about.
It feels like I could fly anywhere, it's so wonderful.
How about it? Want to drink too, Yuu-kun?
You'll pass?
Haha!
Could it be that innocent Yuu-kun is worried about an indirect kiss?
Oh, come on, at this point?
Between you and me...
Is it a no-go because you're a student?
Oh, please.
Don't be so uptight.
You silly~
Tickle tickle tickle
Just because you can't drink my alcohol...
You, you, you, you, you, you
You, you, you, you, you
Oops-
Ah, ah, ah!
Oh no!
It's cold-
Ah, aah!
I'm sorry! Ow, ow, ow...
Thank you, Yuu-kun.
For protecting me...
Ah... ah...
Yuu-kun's lips...
They're so close I can feel your breath...
Ah...
Oh, no, it's just... your breath tickles, Yuu-kun.
Suddenly getting all serious like that...
Don't ask me things like that every single time, geez.
Yuu-kun...
Hehe...
That was such a tender kiss.
Even so, for just a moment, my mind went completely blank.
But you know, Yuu-kun...
Don't you think your kissing is getting better and better?
You haven't been kissing anyone else besides me, have you?
Ahaha, you're saying such sweet things.
"There's only Hazuki-sensei for me," huh?
You sure know how to sweet-talk a woman.
That's right...
Yuu-kun only ever tells the truth, doesn't he?
I know that very well.
But look, we've spilled some alcohol.
Ah, it's all sticky... This feels gross.
Oh, Yuu-kun, you're all sticky too.
Hehe, what a mess we've made of ourselves.
We can't leave our clothes like this. What should we do?
What to do...
Oh, I just had a great idea!
Let's take a bath together and clean off all this stickiness, Yuu-kun!
Now that that's decided, come on, strip, strip!
Gehehe, isn't this great? Isn't it wonderful?
I wonder if it's okay... You'd better join me...
Or I might just go searching for naughty books or DVDs in your room.
Got you!
Now, let's head to the bath together! Let's go!