Huh?
Yuu-kun?
I'm in a bathrobe... on a bed?
What's going on here?
My memory's a bit hazy...
That's right, I suddenly got sleepy in the bath...
Well, I guess it wasn't so sudden after all.
After drinking that much and then suddenly taking a hot bath,
The alcohol hit me all at once, didn't it?
Ah, Yuu-kun, you don't need to apologize.
It's all my fault.
Thank you for getting me out.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
So, did you take a good look?
At my... bare naked body?
Seeing as I was naked in the bath,
And now I am here wearing a bathrobe...
I wonder what that implies...
Yuu-kun, you were desperately trying not to look at me in the bath,
But you must have seen when you dressed me, right?
My naked body~
Wowee, Yuu-kun, your face is bright red!
So? How was it? My nude bod.
I wonder if it's still burned into your eyelids?
Hmm~~?
For Yuu-kun who makes such excuses...
Yuu-kun...
Kissing Yuu-kun...
It feels so good...
My mind...
My body...
My heart is melting...
It's okay.
We won't be disturbed until morning.
Just you and me, Yuu-kun.
Feel me to your heart's content.
Let me feel you too.
Five more minutes...
Ahh... Yuu-kun...
Yeah, I'm awake.
But it still feels like I'm dreaming.
You were so wonderful last night, Yuu-kun.
I'm so happy.
Yes, of course.
You kissed me as much as you wanted.
Hehe, I understand.
But only until your mother comes home, okay?
Ah... Yuu-kun... I love you...
Yuu-kun's kisses... are so gentle...
I'm yours and only yours... forever and ever...
From now on too... okay?
Let's always be this lovey-dovey, alright?